Guide to the School of Architecture, Yale University, Photographs of Events, Activities, and Individuals
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Images of events and activities, 1999-2003; Accession 2007-A-203
  - 1999-2000
    - Frank Gehry Studio Mid-Term Review, 2002 March 7 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Lise Anne Couture Studio Mid-Term Review, 2002 March 7 (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Zaha Hadid Studio Mid-Term Review, 2002 March 8 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Greg Lynn Mid-Term Review, 2002 March 8 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Stefan Tischer Lecture and Recpetion, 2002 March 25 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - George Hargreaves Lecture and Reception, 2002 April 1 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Zaha Hadid Lecture and Reception, 2002 April 4 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Frank Gehry Studio Review with Richard Serra, 2002 April 4 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Cartography Symposium, 2002 April 5 (Box 9, Folder 71)
    - Jorg Schlaich Lecture and Reception, 2002 April 8 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Thomas Krens Lecture and Reception, 2002 April 15 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Sylvia Lavin Lecture and Reception, 2002 April 18 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - 502b 1stYear Building Project Final Selection, 2002 April 25 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - 504b Final Review, 2002 April 29 (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Frank Gehry Studio Final Review, 2002 May 1 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Steven Harris Studio Final Review, 2002 May 1 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Thesis Final Review, 2002 May 1 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Zaha Hadid Studio Final Review, 2002 May 2 (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Greg Lynn Studio Final Review, 2002 May 2 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Deborah Berke Studio Final Review, 2002 May 3 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Lise Anne Couture Studio Final Presentation, 2002 May 3 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - 681b Furniture Final Review, 2002 May 12 (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Commencement, 2002 May 27 (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Studio Life I, 2002 October 9 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Advanced Studio Lottery, 2002 September 5 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Joseph Rose Lecture and Reception, 2002 September 9 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Hillary Brown Lecture, 2002 September 15 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Dense Cities Symposium - Winy Maas Keynote, 2002 September 20 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Dense Cities Symposium, 2002 September 21 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Louisa Hutton and Mathias Sauerbruch Lecture and Reception, 2002 September 30 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - 1sy Year Building Project Open House Reception, 2002 October 1 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Julie Snow Lecture, 2002 October 3 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Toshiko Mori Lecture, 2002 October 21 (Box 10, Folder 77)
  - Digital images (Box 11)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original born digital files, as well as preservation masters, may not be accessed due to their fragility. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist request that they be made. Born digital files cannot be accessed remotely. System requirements include a Manuscripts and Archives computer and file viewing software.
    - Studio Lottery, 2003 January 13; computer files (JPEG)
      General note
      Contact Public Services (phone: 203 432-1735, e-mail: mssa.reference@yale.edu) for information on accessing this digital object.
    - Leslie Robertson, 2003 January 20; computer files (JPEG)
    - James Wines Lecture, 2003 January 23; computer files (JPEG)
    - Brian Tolle Lecture, 2003 January 30; computer files (JPEG)
    - Peter Latz Lecture, 2003 February 27; computer files (JPEG)
    - Mid-Term Review
      - 494b, 2003 March 3; computer files (JPEG)
      - 504b, 2003 March 3; computer files (JPEG)
      - 504b, 2003 March 4; computer files (JPEG)
      - Easterling, 2003 March 5; computer files (JPEG)
      - Bruder, 2003 March 6; computer files (JPEG)
      - Lynn, 2003 March 6; computer files (JPEG)
      - 648b, 2003 March 7; computer files (JPEG)
      - 802b, 2003 March 7; computer files (JPEG)
      - Maas, 2003 March 7; computer files (JPEG)
      - Porphyrios, 2003 March 7; computer files (JPEG)
      - Williams-Tsien, 2003 March 7; computer files (JPEG)
    - Peter Walker Lecture, 2003 March 24; computer files (JPEG)
    - Ken Smith Lecture, 2003 March 27; computer files (JPEG)
    - 502b review, 2003 March 31; computer files (JPEG)
    - Roger Connah Lecture, 2003 March 31; computer files (JPEG)
    - Williams-Tsien Lecture, 2003 April 3; computer files (JPEG)
    - Global Practice Symposium, 2003 April 4; computer files (JPEG)
    - Global Practice Symposium, 2003 April 5; computer files (JPEG)
    - Belmont Freeman Lecture, 2003 April 7; computer files (JPEG)
    - Preston Scott Cohen Lecture, 2003 April 10; computer files (JPEG)
    - Bernard Tschumi, 2003 April 14; computer files (JPEG)
    - Enrique Norten Lecture, 2003 April 17; computer files (JPEG)
    - Final Review
      - 506b, 2003 April 24; computer files (JPEG)
      - 251b Final Review, 2003 April 28; computer files (JPEG)
      - 504b Final Review, 2003 April 29; computer files (JPEG)
      - Turner Brooks, 2003 April 30; computer files (JPEG)
      - Keller Easterling, 2003 May 1; computer files (JPEG)
      - Will Bruder, 2003 May 1; computer files (JPEG)
      - Tom Beeby, 2003 May 2; computer files (JPEG)
      - Williams-Tsien, 2003 May 2; computer files (JPEG)
      - Winy Maas, 2003 May 2; computer files (JPEG)
    - 1st Yr Bldg Project, 2002 October 1; computer files (JPEG)
    - Snow, Julie Lecture, 2002 October 3; computer files (JPEG)
    - 661a, 2002 October 4; computer files (JPEG)
    - 674a Wall Shelf, 2002 October 4; computer files (JPEG)
    - Mid-term
      - 501a, 2002 October 14; computer files (JPEG)
      - 501a mid-term, 2002 October 15; computer files (JPEG)
      - 503a mid-term, 2002 October 15; computer files (JPEG)
      - 503a mid-term, 2002 October 16; computer files (JPEG)
      - 801a review, 2002 October 17; computer files (JPEG)
      - Eisenman mid-term, 2002 October 17; computer files (JPEG)
      - Murcutt mid-term, 2002 October 17; computer files (JPEG)
      - Balmond mid-term, 2002 October 18; computer files (JPEG)
      - Krier mid-term, 2002 October 18; computer files (JPEG)
      - Plattus mid-term, 2002 October 18; computer files (JPEG)
      - Post Pro mid-term, 2002 October 18; computer files (JPEG)
    - Toshiko Mori Lecture, 2002 October 21; computer files (JPEG)
    - 674a Umbrella Stand, 2002 October 22; computer files (JPEG)
    - Balmond Lecture, 2002 October 28; computer files (JPEG)
    - Kieran-Timberlake Lecture, 2002 November 4; computer files (JPEG)
    - Murcutt Lecture, 2002 November 7; computer files (JPEG)
    - Eisenman, Krier, 2002 November 8; computer files (JPEG)
    - Eisenman, Krier, 2002 November 9; computer files (JPEG)
    - 674a 4th Peppermill, 2002 November 12; computer files (JPEG)
    - Short, Alan Lecture, 2002 November 14; computer files (JPEG)
    - Hopkins, Michael Lecture, 2002 November 18; computer files (JPEG)
    - Daniels, Klaus Lecture, 2002 November 21; computer files (JPEG)
    - Final Review
      - 249a, 2002 December 4; computer files (JPEG)
      - 450a, 2002 December 6; computer files (JPEG)
      - 250a, 2002 December 9; computer files (JPEG)
      - 501a, 2002 December 9; computer files (JPEG)
      - 501a, 2002 December 10; computer files (JPEG)
      - 503a, 2002 December 10; computer files (JPEG)
      - 523a, 2002 December 11; computer files (JPEG)
      - 523a, 2002 December 12; computer files (JPEG)
      - Eisenman, 2002 December 12; computer files (JPEG)
      - Murcutt, 2002 December 12; computer files (JPEG)
      - Balmond, 2002 December 13; computer files (JPEG)
      - Krier, 2002 December 13; computer files (JPEG)
      - Plattus, 2002 December 13; computer files (JPEG)
    - 674a Collapsible Seat, 2002 December 17; computer files (JPEG)
- Photographs documenting facilities, faculty, and students, circa 1960-2008; Accession 2009-A-054
  - Art and Architecture building renovation, photographs by Peter Aaron, 2007 August (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Art and Architecture building interior, photographs by Richard Barnes, 2007 May (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Digital copies, 20; 20 computer files (JPEG)
  - Peter Mullard, faculty, circa 1960s (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class photos, 2004-2008 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Computer files (Box 2)